<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">P4_Cities_JavierVictorGloria</string>

    <!-- Cities -->
    <string name="rotterdam">Rotterdam</string>
    <string name="holanda">Netherlands</string>
    <string name="algeciras">Algeciras</string>
    <string name="espana">Spain</string>
    <string name="oran">Oran</string>
    <string name="argelia">Algeria</string>
    <string name="santos">Santos</string>
    <string name="brasil">Brazil</string>
    <string name="hong_kong">Hong Kong</string>

    <!-- Countries -->
    <string name="china">China</string>
    <string name="europa">Europe</string>
    <string name="africa">Africa</string>
    <string name="samerica">South America</string>
    <string name="asia">Asia</string>

    <!-- Places -->
    <string name="markthal">Markthal</string>
    <string name="desc_markthal">An iconic indoor market where modern architecture meets tradition. Under its impressive giant mural called \"The Horn of Plenty\", you can taste dishes from all over the world at its numerous fresh food stalls and gourmet restaurants specialized in international cuisine.</string>

    <string name="casas_cubo">Cube Houses</string>
    <string name="desc_casas_cubo">Designed by architect Piet Blom, these innovative homes are tilted 45 degrees to optimize urban space. They represent an \"urban forest\" concept where each house is a tree and the complex forms a unique avant-garde structure.</string>

    <string name="puente_erasmo">Erasmus Bridge</string>
    <string name="desc_puente_erasmo">An impressive cable-stayed bridge popularly known as \"The Swan\" due to the elegant shape of its white steel pylon. It connects the north and south of the city, offering one of the most recognizable and modern silhouettes of the Rotterdam skyline.</string>

    <string name="euromast">Euromast</string>
    <string name="desc_euromast">This observation tower is the tallest structure in the city. It offers the best 360-degree panoramic views over the port and surroundings, also featuring a luxury restaurant located high up for an unforgettable dining experience.</string>

    <string name="zoo_rotterdam">Rotterdam Zoo</string>
    <string name="desc_zoo">Diergaarde Blijdorp is one of the oldest and most beautiful zoos in the Netherlands. Its Oceanium stands out, a spectacular underwater tunnel where you can walk surrounded by sharks, rays, and sea turtles in a fascinating environment.</string>

    <string name="playa_getares">Getares Beach</string>
    <string name="desc_getares">A semi-urban beach famous for its privileged views of the Strait of Gibraltar and its family atmosphere. Its crystal-clear waters and its lively promenade make it the perfect place to enjoy the sun and the Andalusian sea breeze.</string>

    <string name="plaza_alta">High Square</string>
    <string name="desc_plaza_alta">The authentic heart of the city, decorated with vibrant typical Andalusian tiles and a historical central fountain. It is the quintessential social meeting point, surrounded by emblematic buildings and palm trees.</string>

    <string name="parque_cristina">Maria Cristina Park</string>
    <string name="desc_parque">An oasis of tranquility with historical gardens located in the city center. Opened in the 19th century, it features shaded walks, busts of illustrious figures, and a central gazebo that provides a haven of peace and freshness.</string>

    <string name="puerto_algeciras">Port of Algeciras</string>
    <string name="desc_puerto">One of the most important commercial and passenger ports in Europe and the Mediterranean. Its magnitude is impressive, being a key economic engine where the constant traffic of ships creates a dynamic industrial landscape.</string>

    <string name="mercado_abastos">Abastos Market</string>
    <string name="desc_mercado">An engineering masterpiece designed by Eduardo Torroja. Its spectacular laminar dome, which in its day was the largest in the world without internal supports, today houses the most traditional fresh local product stalls.</string>

    <string name="fuerte_santa_cruz">Fort of Santa Cruz</string>
    <string name="desc_santa_cruz">This historical fort built by the Spaniards rises majestically over Mount Murdjadjo. It offers spectacular and strategic views of the port and the entire city, serving as a living testimony to Oran\'s military past.</string>

    <string name="mezquita_pasha">Hassan Pasha Mosque</string>
    <string name="desc_mezquita">A true architectural gem from the Ottoman period built in 1796. It stands out for its octagonal minaret decorated with tiles and its elegant interior courtyard, reflecting the richness of Islamic art.</string>

    <string name="catedral_oran">Sacred Heart Cathedral</string>
    <string name="desc_catedral">A former neo-Byzantine style Catholic cathedral now converted into an impressive public library. Its detailed reliefs and grand structure make it one of the most iconic and photogenic buildings in the city.</string>

    <string name="front_de_mer">Front de Mer</string>
    <string name="desc_front_mer">Oran\'s emblematic promenade, ideal for walking and enjoying the Mediterranean breeze. It is lined with French colonial buildings and numerous terraces where locals gather to watch the sunset.</string>

    <string name="palacio_bey">Bey\'s Palace</string>
    <string name="desc_palacio_bey">A historical residence showing the elegance and refinement of Islamic art. Its courtyards, pavilions, and gardens transport the visitor to the era of the Beylicate of Oran, offering a journey full of fascinating details.</string>

    <string name="museo_cafe">Coffee Museum</string>
    <string name="desc_museo_cafe">Located in the luxurious former Coffee Exchange building, this museum tells the global importance of this bean for Brazil\'s development. It is a place full of history where coffee aroma and marble architecture merge.</string>

    <string name="jardin_playa">Beach Gardens</string>
    <string name="desc_jardin_santos">Holds the Guinness World Record for being the longest beachfront garden in the world. There are 7 kilometers of impeccable lawn, exotic flowers, and fountains that separate the city from the sand.</string>

    <string name="monte_serrat">Mount Serrat</string>
    <string name="desc_monte_serrat">Accessible via a picturesque historical funicular, this point offers the best views of the entire city and the immense port of Santos. At the top, there is a sanctuary dedicated to the city\'s patron saint.</string>

    <string name="estadio_santos">Vila Belmiro Stadium</string>
    <string name="desc_estadio">The legendary football field where Pelé made history with Santos FC. It is a temple for sports lovers, featuring a museum that exhibits the trophies and golden history of one of Brazil\'s most famous clubs.</string>

    <string name="acuario_santos">Santos Aquarium</string>
    <string name="desc_acuario">The first municipal aquarium in Brazil, housing hundreds of marine and freshwater species. It is a reference educational center where you can see penguins, sea lions, and a great variety of fish.</string>

    <string name="victoria_peak">Victoria Peak</string>
    <string name="desc_victoria_peak">The highest point on Hong Kong Island and its most popular attraction. It offers incredible views of the financial center skyscrapers and Victoria Harbour, especially spectacular at dusk when the lights come on</string>

    <string name="buda_gigante">Tian Tan Buddha</string>
    <string name="desc_buda">A huge 34-meter high bronze statue located in the quiet mountains of Lantau Island. It represents harmony between man and nature, and to reach its base you must climb an impressive 268-step staircase.</string>

    <string name="star_ferry">Star Ferry</string>
    <string name="desc_ferry">This historical ferry service crosses Victoria Harbour connecting Kowloon with Hong Kong Island. It offers one of the most picturesque and economical journeys in the world, showing the skyline from the water.</string>

    <string name="temple_street">Temple Street Night Market</string>
    <string name="desc_temple">A vibrant night market famous for its bustling atmosphere, delicious street food, and numerous souvenir and electronics stalls. It is the perfect place to experience the night energy of Hong Kong.</string>

    <string name="avenue_stars">Avenue of Stars</string>
    <string name="desc_avenue_stars">A tribute to Hong Kong cinema located on the Tsim Sha Tsui waterfront. It includes iconic statues like Bruce Lee\'s and offers the best spot to enjoy the city\'s daily light and sound show.</string>

    //HomeView
    <string name="ciudad_anterior">Previous City</string>
    <string name="ciudad_siguiente">Next City</string>
    <string name="lugar_aleatorio">Random Place</string>
    <string name="mas_opciones"> More options</string>
    <string name="compartir">Share</string>
    <string name="acerca_de">About</string>

    //LugarView
    <string name="ubicacion">VIEW LOCATION</string>

    <!-- Categories -->
    <string name="todo_lugar">All</string>
    <string name="cafeterias">Cafés</string>
    <string name="restaurantes">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="centros_comerciales">Shopping Centers</string>
    <string name="parques">Parks</string>

    <!-- CityView -->
    <string name="descubre_lugares_preciosos">Discover beautiful places</string>
    <string name="puntos_interes">Points of interest</string>
    <string name="pulsar_para_informacion">Click to discover more</string>

</resources>
